allaccess.com 2015-06-26

# All Access Music Group, Inc. Privacy Policy | Free Online Membership

  * ##### Last Updated: July 18, 2007

##### AllAccess.com Web Site Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") governs your use of this web site ([allaccess.com](http://allaccess.com/)) (the "Web Site"), published and maintained by All Access Music Group, Inc., with offices at 28955 Pacific Coast Highway, Suite 210-5, Malibu, CA 90265 (" **AA** ," " **we** ," " **us** ," " **our** ," or other similar pronouns). By visiting this Web Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our Web Site this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the AA Terms of Service, which governs your use of this Web Site in general. This Web Site is intended for users who are of majority in the local jurisdiction in which they reside (and at least 18 years old). Unless otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy solely to information collected on the Web Site and does not apply to information we may collect by other means. This Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States, regardless of the location of individual users.

##### Summary

By providing you with notice of its information practices, AA demonstrates its commitment to protecting consumer privacy. Accordingly, AA DOES NOT extract, without permission, Personal Information (as defined below) about you or your computer at any time while on AA's Web Site, except for Personal Information that is actively provided through registration, logging in and out, online forms or other means. AA will, however, analyze information about our visitors as a group to make our Web Site better, but visitors are not individually identified when we do so.

All marketing efforts we undertake are targeted toward a business audience only. Children under thirteen (13) years of age are strictly prohibited from using the Web Site.

##### Your California Privacy Rights

The following applies solely to California residents who have an established business relationship with AA. If we collect Personal Information from you, we may make that Personal Information available our affiliated companies, or to other third parties who have products or services that we believe will be of interest to you, for their marketing and promotional purposes. If you later decide that you do not want us to share your Personal Information with these companies for their marketing and promotional purposes, visit our marketing preferences page at www.allaccess.com/preferences/ or by sending an e-mail to online support@allaccess.com. In this e-mail, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from AA in general, or just via e-mail, postal mail, instant messaging, and/or by phone, (ii) you would only like to opt-out of certain of AA's e-newsletters or correspondence, and if so which ones, and/or (iii) you would like to elect for AA not to share your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing purposes. Your opt out request will be processed within thirty (30) days of the date on which we receive it. For more information on how your Personal Information is collected, used and shared, please read the remainder of this Privacy Policy.

##### Information We Collect

AA may collect a variety of statistical data about its Web Site visitors. This data includes the source IP address (as further described below in the IP Address and Clickstream Data section, below) of the visitor, the time of visit, the areas of the site visited and information about browser, operating system and other system parameters. As of the date of this Privacy Policy, none of this information is used to personally identify any individual visitor, and is used solely for the purposes of analyzing overall traffic and usage patterns. However, AA reserves the right to begin matching such usage data with an individual's Personal Information subsequent to the date of this Privacy Policy.

In order to make your visits to our Web Site and use of the services available on or through our Web Site as worthwhile as possible, AA may also collect Personal Information about its visitors, but only when a visitor voluntarily provides such Personal Information to us in the process of ordering subscriptions, entering contests or sweepstakes, signing up for our AllAccess Newsletter, using our forums, emailing the Web Site, registering with the Web Site or using other services available on or through our Web Site. The information that you give us and information about your order, purchases or other activities on the Web Site may be combined with other Personal Information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. "Personal Information" includes, for example, names, postal addresses, e-mail addresses, wireless addresses, age, credit card and other payment information, demographic information, purchase history, subscription information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual. Only AA has access to individual account information. This information is used internally by AA to fulfill your requests and for marketing and research purposes.

If, at the time of your registration, you elect to receive the AllAccess Newsletter, AA will use your information to send you email. From time to time, AA or our partners, as further described herein, may also send you information on products and special offers that we believe will be of interest to you. If you do not wish to continue receiving these special offers, please see the Right to Opt Out section, below. Certain areas of the Web Site may require additional user registration in order to gain access. Please take note that the advertisers and partners of AA may have differing privacy policies and it is your responsibility to take the time to read each of them.

##### Right to Opt Out

You have the right to opt-out of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Web Site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to: (1) receive correspondence from us, or (2) have your Personal Information shared with other entities (outside of AA) for their marketing purposes. You may also make this request by visiting our marketing preferences Web page at www.allaccess.com/preferences/ or by sending an e-mail to support@allaccess.com. In this e-mail, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from AA in general, or just via e-mail, postal mail, instant messaging, and/or by phone, (ii) you would only like to opt-out of certain of AA's e-newsletters or correspondence, and if so which ones, and/or (iii) you would like to elect for AA not to share your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing purposes.

Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.

##### Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

AA may use cookies to enhance a visitor's online experience by making it easier to navigate through our Web Site or to make an activity work better.

Cookies are small pieces of information or data files that are sent through your browser or related software from a Web server and are stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies may be used to track where you travel on our Web Site and what you look at and purchase, and they allow a computer to "remember" information from our Web Site for future use. The use of cookies is an industry standard and is practiced by most major web sites. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are, but they may enable us to relate your use of our Web Site to other information, including your Personal Information, which you have provided to us when you registered or performed other activities while visiting our Web Site. All of these purposes serve to enhance your experience while using our services in the ways described below.

Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. Additionally, if you have a flash player installed on your computer, your flash player can be set to reject or delete flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Web Site or certain areas or features of the Web Site.

We also may use clear GIFs (aka web beacons or pixel tags) or similar technologies, in the Web Site and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a page of the Web Site or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. A clear gif may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.

We may use cookies and other tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: (i) keeping count of return visits to our Web Site or our advertisers' or partners' sites; (ii) accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on website and advertisement usage; (iii) determining which features our customers like best; (iv) saving your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our Web Site.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

##### IP Address and Clickstream Data

Our server automatically collects data about your server's Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an IP Address, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you're on the Internet. When you request pages from our Web Site, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Web Site; the web site you visit after this Web Site; the advertisements you see and/or click on; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Web Site or a referral site; and other web usage activity and data logged by our web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet service provider. Although we do not as of the date of this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to link this information with your Personal Information.

Any or all of these activities with regard to our Web Site usage information (information gathered through the use of cookies, web bugs and clickstream data) may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

##### How AA Uses Personal Information

Personal Information is used to enhance and custom-tailor each user's experience on the Web Site and his or her use of our services. Such information may be used to determine what Web Site content is of interest to which users, what types of newsletters and other communications are appropriate for individual users, and to identify user-generated content such as message board postings, votes in online polls and participation in online games. Such information may also be used, for example, to process your orders, respond to your requests and inquiries and provide you with the services and features offered on or through our Web Site.

AA may also use Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We reserve the right to match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Web Site usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt-out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section, above.

In addition, AA may use Personal Information to generate aggregate data about our Web Site's visitors.

##### Correspondence and Newsletters

AA uses automated e-mail systems to e-mail the AllAccess Newsletter and to collect and answer correspondence from our visitors. AA tries to make it easy for you to contact us and we provide easy instructions on our Web Site on how you can either edit Personal Information previously given (such as your address) or opt out of receiving any automated messages generated by AA. For more information on opting out, please see the Right to Opt Out section, above. Should you have a technical problem doing this please contact support@allaccess.com.

##### How AA Shares Information Collected Online

AA does not buy, sell, or trade consumer mailing lists. All marketing efforts we undertake are targeted toward a business audience only. Notwithstanding the above, AA may, however, share aggregate information about all users of our Web Site, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user, with our advertisers, business partners, sponsors and certain others, as further described below herein.

AA may also share your Personal Information with our advertisers, business partners, sponsors and certain others, who may send you offers so long as you have not opted out of receiving such offers, as further described in Third Party Offers, below.

##### Public Forums

When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Web Site, such as a chat forum, bulletin board, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum that we may make available on or through our Web Site, the information that you submit will be made available to the general public. For this reason, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information, including your full name, home address, phone number, other information that would enable other users to locate you, or financial information on these areas of our Web Site. Instead, you should make up a username that does not disclose your personal identity.

##### Third Party Offers

Unless you have unchecked the designated box during registration to opt out from receiving certain information or made such changes in your preferences located at www.allaccess.com/preferences/, we may provide you offers from other entities (outside of the Web Site) who have products and services that we think might be of interest to you. Additionally, we may from time to time provide your Personal Information to these entities so that they may send you these offers. If you change your mind and no longer want us to share your Personal Information with these types of third parties, follow the instructions to opt-out in the Right to Opt Out section, above.

##### Advertisers and Third Party "Linked-To" Web Sites

AA may include advertisements and/or links to other web sites operated by third parties that are not sponsors and are not affiliated with AA. AA is not responsible for the content, practices, or information provided or requested on Web sites operated by third parties. Further, advertisements on and links to or from www.allaccess.com do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by AA of the content, policies, practices, products or services offered on such third party web sites.

##### Service Providers

We may use third parties to help operate our Web Site and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Web Site or for our business (such as web site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

##### Legally Compelled Disclosures

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may also report information about your account to credit bureaus. Late payments, missed payments, or other defaults on your account may be reflected in your credit report.

##### Business Transfer

In the event that AA, or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

##### Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (generally not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear gifs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear gifs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message).

##### Wireless Addresses

If the email address you provide to us is a wireless email address, you agree to receive messages at such address from AA (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard or premium rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

##### Security

The importance of security for all Personal Information associated with visitors to our Web Site is of utmost concern to us. AA exercises great care and implements a variety of technologies in an effort to help make the Web Site secure against unauthorized access and to protect the Personal Information visitors choose to provide to us. AA periodically reviews and updates these measures. Unfortunately, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure, and AA cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. As a result, while AA strives to protect a visitor's Personal Information, AA cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us or from our online products or services, and a visitor does so at his/her own risk.

If you contact us by e-mail or a "contact us" or similar feature on our Web Site, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by such methods, from which you may receive unsolicited communications.

You may create an account on our Web Site with a username and password. If so, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Web Site by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify AA of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify AA when you desire to cancel your account on this Web Site. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision.

We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at support@allaccess.com with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.

##### Review and Deletion of Personal Information

You may review and delete the Personal Information about you that is contained in your user account at AA at any time on your preferences page located at www.allaccess.com/preferences/.

##### Consent to Processing

By providing Personal Information to this Web Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

##### Children

Special notice for users under the age of majority and their parents: The Web Site is not intended for use by children, and any use by children under the age of 13 is strictly prohibited. Any attempt to register with the Web Site using an age under 13 years will be automatically rejected. AA does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

AA reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Web Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Web Site. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Web Site or sending you an e-mail.

##### Questions, Concerns and Comments

Please contact us at [support@allaccess.com](mailto:support@allaccess.com) or write to us at: Business & Legal Affairs, AllAccess.com Inc., 28955 Pacific Coast Highway, Suite 210-5, Malibu, CA 90265 with any questions regarding this Privacy Policy.
